# CURRICULUM VITAE - ODUOLA TIMOTHY TUMININU

## **Personal Details:**

Address: 67, Irepodun Zone C, Igisogba, Oremeji, Ibadan, Oyo, Nigeria

Contact number: +234(0)8069647802 Email: +234(0)8069647802 timmyther02@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 2<sup>nd</sup> January, 1993

State of Origin: Oyo

#### **Profile:**

I have a do-it-yourself experience in computer networking, UI/UX design, website development, garnered some personal experience in software engineering and testing using Visual Studio code as well as 1+ year of coding experience with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React JS.

### **Education Qualification:**

# **Professional Qualification:**

- National Youth Service Corps Certificate
- National Youth Service Corps (SAED) Certificate
- Health Safety and Environment (HSE 1-3)

#### **Technical Skills and Abilities:**

- Microsoft Office suite
- Corel Draw
- Figma
- · Website development
- UI/UX Design
- Microsoft Word and Excel

### Work Experience:

2019 - 2020

Kwara State College of Education (Technical), Lafiagi. - Computer Operator

2017

Broadcasting Cooperation of Oyo State (B.C.O.S) - Industry Training

2010 - 2013

Goshen International Comprehensive School

- Teacher

# **Project(s) Worked On:**

Project Name:

Intrascaping.

Project Description:

This is a marketplace website, develop with WordPress that would display the available Landscaping Job and Landscaper with their prices, accept service order and quantity, then displays the invoice and prints it if the customer is eventually hiring their service.

**Project Duration:** 

Aug. 2020-Sept. 2020

Involvement:

Development and uploading into the server.

# Language(s):

Native Language: Yoruba,

Formal Language: English (Spoken and Written).

## **Referees:**

1. Mrs. O. A. Oladejo Goshen International Comprehensive School, Ibadan +23408032176734,

2. Mall. Yusuf Abdullahi

Kwara State College of Education (Technical), Lafiagi +23408034237120